groupcard.com 2018-03-16

# GroupCard - Privacy Policy

WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS  
This privacy policy pertains to the use of all services related to Interactive Gift Corporation (IGC), including the IGC web site at [www.GroupCard.com](http://www.groupcard.com/)

This privacy policy covers how IGC treats personal information that IGC collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable including but not limited to your name, address, email address, or phone number.

Children under 13 are not permitted to use any IGC services, and so this privacy policy makes no provision for children's use of the site.

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND HOW IT IS USED  
General Information   
IGC collects personal information when you register with IGC services, when you use IGC services or when you post content on IGC. We receive and store any information you enter on our services or give us in any other way.

When you register we may ask for your email address and certain optional information such as your name, birth date, birth place, gender, biographical information, ICQ/AIM/Yahoo/MSN user name, and personal interests. We probably won't ask you for all of this though.

IGC automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie, and the page you request.

IGC uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting.

IP Addresses   
IP Addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in our user registration databases when you register with IGC.

IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including:

To diagnose or service technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.

To tailor advertising based on geographic area or other information derived from your IP address. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.

To estimate the total number of users visiting IGC from specific geographical regions.

To make sure that people are not voting for themselves or friends during contests or promotions.

Cookies   
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.

If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use IGC products or services that require you to "sign in", and you may not be able to take full advantage of the IGC service.

IGC uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

Access your information when you "sign in".

Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using IGC's services.

Display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on IGC.

Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.

Conduct research to improve IGC's content and services.

IGC may let other companies (such as Google) that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other entities' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other entities do not have access to IGC's cookies.

Email   
If you provide your email address in the course of using the IGC web site, IGC will store your email address along with a password for later use. This allows IGC to; customize your web site experience, give you the ability to edit content that you have previously created, and accumulate all of your cards on one web page for your convenience. You may reset your password at any time.

Your email address is displayed as the "from" email address when you; invite others to sign a card, send a card to a recipient, or send a group thank-you message after receiving a card.

IGC allows you to opt into an event-reminder email program. Currently this program is used to send you an email notice when your friends (those who are connected to you through a private card) have upcoming birthdays. IGC may expand this program to include weddings, new babies, graduations, holidays, and other events as appropriate. IGC may also send you updates about new features, promotions, or contests as part of this event-reminder option. IGC will endeavor to make this optional program a value to you. You may opt-out of this service at any time by following the steps below.

OPT-OUT  
While IGC does not give you the opportunity to remove your information from our database, you may remove certain information by contacting us directly at [feedback@groupcard.com](mailto:feedback@groupcard.com). This includes electing not to receive future company communications or marketing material from IGC or to opting to discontinue use of our service. Note that we cannot control whether another GroupCard.com user contacts you or sends you a GroupCard.com invitation using our service.

Additionally, you may opt out of receiving emails from IGC using our unsubscribe page at www.groupcard.com/unsub.php

INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE  
If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

IGC may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the IGC Terms of Service.

IGC may share demographic information with business partners. No personally identifiable information will ever be used without your permission (i.e. we will ask you for a quote or testimonial)

IGC does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested or when we have your permission.

It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of IGC's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We will transfer information about you if IGC is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, IGC will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the IGC web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
IGC may update this policy at any time for any reason.

**Questions**  
If you have questions or suggestions you can contact us at:  
Interactive Gift Corporation, GroupCard.com

Click here to contact us or you may even contact us through [feedback@groupcard.com](mailto:feedback@groupcard.com)
